bollywoodlyrics.com 2004-06-05

# Welcome to BollywoodLyrics.com - Free Song Lyrics from Old and New Hindi Films

The following privacy policy is for the **BollywoodLyrics.com** website. 

Advertisements of the following companies may appear on our site:   
ClickAgents - Their [Privacy Policy](http://www.clickagents.com/privacy.phtml)  
Commission Junction - Their [Privacy Policy](http://www.cj.com/)  
SmasHits.com - Their Privacy Policy

Ad Banners served by these companies may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information. 

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

All personal information collected on this site will be utilized primarily for internal purposes and/or to enhance visitor enjoyment and experience. We may also use email addresses or other personally identifiable information to contact visitors who directly communicate with us, For example, to provide a requested email newsletter or song. Visitors may voluntarily subscribe to newsletters. We provide visitors with an option to unsubscribe from future email newsletters. Sometimes, personal information submitted by visitors may be used for marketing and promotional purposes relating to the Web site or other entertainment properties. We don't share any personally identifiable information provided by visitors with third parties. We bear no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information visitors may disclose on the bulletin boards. 

**SECURITY**

We don't share any personally identifiable information provided by visitors with third parties, unless specified at time of collection. All information that is submitted on our site is stored securely and not shared with third parties. 

**COOKIES**

Various methods are employed to gather data. "Cookies" are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are "small strings of text" that are stored in your computer through the web browser; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so. 

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to gather site statistics. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. 

We reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. 

Please contact us for more information.
